{
    "id": "0d56153f3a124f9aab804ca8bfe7e674",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I told him why I ............................... that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "did",
                "will do"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06fa2bfb2def487aaed847ad53d10774"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked the boys whether they .................................... the problems.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "solved",
                "have solved",
                "had solved"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "889c81c186ef4f5aaa23ddf842e46cf7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will go home during the vacation so that I ...................................... my brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can see",
                "could see",
                "might see"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd299fa367fe44a5a8ab62e63d4abd27"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although they ......................................, they did not lose heart.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "defeated",
                "had defeated",
                "were defeated"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "31a97189d7724788b4b1a90d093160f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our teacher taught us that virtue ...................................... its own reward.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1e10c94f5c204f42a750e019b7a25f16"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our holy books tell us that man .................................. mortal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "will be"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4bb73ab3430b4cf29023a71c8980f151"
        },
        {
            "question": "Just as I entered the room, the bell ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ring",
                "rang",
                "rung"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f1a627b073ca4ea492d8ae5163a55562"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will break your neck if you ...................................... that again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "did",
                "had done"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "68d892c102b3443ba2aeb621af6e2bc6"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house where James ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "is living"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5998930f205e437d8e1678e364deea30"
        },
        {
            "question": "He declared that he will not believe it even if he ....................................... it with his own eyes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sees",
                "saw",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "482ffed9e7c84b12bf6cf762f496cf99"
        }
    ]
}